https://www.parexel.com/company/trust-and-privacy/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
HomeAbout UsTrust and PrivacyPrivacy Policy
Web Sites Privacy Commitment
This Privacy Policy was last updated in October 2020
Parexel will collect information through its websites that can identify you (if provided by you), such as your name, address, phone number, e-mail address, company name and position. Parexel may use this information to respond to your requests for information, products or services. Parexel may also collect information that will usually not allow us to directly identify you, such as information gathered through "cookies" (see below).
When you contact Parexel via its websites to request or to access information, you are asked to provide your personal information. By providing your personal information to Parexel via its websites, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and to receive communications from Parexel.
The information you provide to us will be available to Parexel, its subsidiaries and third parties working with or on behalf of Parexel. Access to your information and the equipment processing it, is at all times restricted to appropriate staff. Except as set forth in this Privacy Policy, Parexel will not trade, sell, release, share or transfer your personal information for use by any business outside the Parexel organization without your consent, or in a form other than what was disclosed to you at the time the information was collected, unless permitted or required by law.
Parexel reserves the right to disclose all information collected to the extent required by law or to respond to judicial process. Parexel may also provide any or all collected information to a third party in connection with the sale, assignment, or other transfer of the business of the particular website to which the information relates if such third party agrees to treat all such information substantially in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
Parexel takes reasonable measures to maintain the confidentiality of your personal information regardless of the country where such information is stored or transferred to.
In jurisdictions with data protection and privacy laws, and where contractual commitments require, Parexel ensures that individuals can exercise all relevant informational rights with respect to their personal information collected by Parexel via its websites, including, but not limited to, the right of access and correction, to withdraw consent at any time, object to data processing, request data deletion, restrict aspects of data processing, and request transmission of provided personal information in a common digital format (e.g., pdf) to themselves or another organization.
Please keep in mind that Clinical trial / study subjects must contact their investigator at their study site, who will be able to make the necessary link to subject identity as outside of Parexel`s own early phase clinical units, Parexel does not hold information that would allow Parexel to directly identify clinical trial / study subjects.
International Data Transfer
Parexel as global company is committed to the confidentiality, integrity and availability of personal information we process and has in place mechanisms to ensure a compliant transfer of personal information. For example, Parexel has executed Standard Contractual Clauses (“SCC”) or Standard Data Protection Clauses (“SDPC”) adopted by the European Commission (or by a supervisory authority and approved by the European Commission) for the purpose of transferring personal information from the European Economic Area. EU residents whose personal information is transferred by Parexel as controller under SCC or SDPC may request a copy of such SCC or SDPC from Parexel through the contact details listed below.
Information Security
Parexel maintains a reasonable level of physical, electronic and managerial procedures in order to protect the information that it collects from its website. This includes maintaining computer equipment, networks, programs and documentation to a common standard and restricting access to equipment and information to appropriate staff.
Children's Privacy
Parexel does not collect or maintain information at its websites from those it knows are under 13 years of age, and no parts of its websites are structured to attract anyone under the age of 13.
Links to Other Websites
Our websites may contain links to other websites. Please keep in mind when you access websites operated by other parties, whether through links on our websites or otherwise, that we do not control what happens on those websites. You should always check the privacy policy of the website you are visiting in order to be sure you know how the operator of that website will collect information from you and what the operator of that website will do with the information.
Change Notification and Specific Privacy Terms
As we provide more services on our websites and as privacy laws and regulations evolve, it may be necessary to revise or update our Privacy Policy without notice. You can determine if this Privacy Policy has been revised since your last visit by referring to the "last updated" legend at the bottom of this page.  Your use of our website constitutes your acceptance of the terms of the revised Privacy Policy, and you should therefore review the Privacy Policy regularly to ensure that you are aware of its terms.  Please print, save, and retain a copy of the Privacy Policy (and of any revised version) for your records.
Please note that this Privacy Policy does not cover any Parexel affiliate or Parexel line of business that operates under its own separate privacy policy or specific privacy terms that are tailored for the different ways your personal information is collected by different Parexel lines of business such as:
Service Terms address customer data to which we may be provided access in order to perform services;
Recruiting Terms address information we may collect in connection with Parexel´s employment recruiting, clinical trial / study subjects or potential investigator efforts;
Marketing and sales terms address information we may collect in connection with marketing and sales activities; and
Specific web sites’ privacy policies address information we may collect via Parexel`s own early phase clinical units, or Parexel´s Academia.
Inquiries, Complaints and Information Corrections
To be removed from our contact lists, or to make a complaint or submit an inquiry, please write to Parexel at the following address:
Parexel International Corporation
Attn: Webmaster
8 Federal St.
Billerica, MA 01821, USA
Communications, queries or requests to exercise informational rights (e.g., access to data) or complaints can be addressed to the attention of Chief Privacy Officer, Parexel International GmbH, Am Bahnhof Westend 15, D-14059 Berlin, Germany, or emailed to privacy@Parexel.com.
Additional information for inhabitants of the European Economic Area
Communications, queries or requests to exercise informational rights (e.g., access to data) or complaints under the European Union General Data Protection Regulation (European Commission Regulation 2016/679 or GDPR) can also be addressed to the attention of Parexel`s EU Data Protection Officer, via mail to Parexel International GmbH, EU Data Protection Officer / Datenschutzbeauftragter, Am Bahnhof Westend 13, D-14059 Berlin, Germany, or emailed to EU_DPO@Parexel.com.
Within the European Economic Area, individuals have the right in law to complain about how their information is handled to a supervisory authority (data protection authority) that is responsible for regulating compliance with the GDPR. A list of all EU supervisory authorities is available on the European Commission website:
https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en
Additional Information for California Consumers
This section applies solely California consumers (California residents), and explains your rights under the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA).
Sale of Personal Information
In the preceding twelve (12) months, Parexel has not sold personal information.
Access to Specific Information and Data Portability Rights
You have the right to request that Parexel disclose certain information to you about our collection and use of your personal information over the past 12 months. Once we receive your request and confirm your identity, we will disclose to you the information requested, including:
The categories of personal information we collected about you.
The categories of sources of the personal information we collected about you.
Our business purpose for collecting that personal information.
The categories of third parties with whom we share that personal information.
The specific pieces of personal information we collected.
Information about any sales of your personal information.
In addition, upon request we will provide you with a copy of all of your personal information (Data Portability).
Deletion Request Rights
You have the right to request that Parexel delete any of your personal information that we collected from you and retained, subject to certain exceptions. Once we receive your request and confirm your identity, we will delete your personal information from our records, unless an exception applies.  If an exception applies, you will be notified that the data will not be deleted, along with specific information about the basis for the exception.
Exercising Access, Data Portability, and Deletion Rights
To exercise the access, data portability, and deletion rights described above, please submit a request to us by either:
Calling us at +1 (888) 228-7425
Sending an email to privacy@parexel.com, Attn: US Privacy Officer
Only you, or a person registered with the California Secretary of State that you authorize to act on your behalf, may make a request related to your personal information. You may also make a request on behalf of your minor child.
You may only make a request for access or data portability twice within a 12-month period. Your request must:
Provide sufficient information that allows us to reasonably verify you are the person about whom we collected personal information or an authorized representative.
Describe your request with sufficient detail to allows us to properly understand, evaluate, and respond to it.
Provide a means to contact you.
We will only use personal information provided in a CCPA request to verify the requestor’s identity or authority to make the request.
Response Timing
We endeavor to respond to a verifiable consumer request within forty-five (45) days of its receipt. If we require more time (up to 90 days), we will inform you of the reason and extension period in writing.
Fee
We do not charge a fee to process or respond to your CCPA request unless it is excessive, repetitive, or manifestly unfounded. If we determine that the request warrants a fee, we will tell you why we made that decision and provide you with a cost estimate before completing your request.
Contact Information
If you have any questions or comments about this Notice, the ways in which Parexel collects and uses your information described above, your choices and rights regarding such use, or wish to exercise your rights under California law, please do not hesitate to contact us by either:
Calling us at +1 (888) 228-7425
Sending an email to privacy@parexel.com, Attn: US Privacy Officer
Cookies and Other Web Tracking Techniques And How We Use Them
When you use our sites, Parexel will assign cookie files (“cookies”) to you, which are a small amount of information we send to your web browser. Cookies enable the computers operating our websites to differentiate between visitors and to track the patterns of activities engaged in by different visitors. By tracking such activities, the computers operating our websites can recognize a visitor and customize certain features for that visitor. We may also use aggregated, non-identifiable information regarding persons who visit our site in order to learn more about the use of the site and how we can improve it.
You may be able to modify your browser preferences to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. If you choose not to accept cookies, you may not be able to use those functions of the websites that require registration.
We may also receive IP addresses in the normal course of the operation of our website. An IP address is a number assigned to you by your Internet service provider so you can access the Internet. Although we do receive IP addresses, we do not use them to identify you personally or disclose them to others.
This website uses the following web analytic tools. The tools use cookies to help the web team analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookies about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by the following companies under their privacy policies:
You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however, please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website.
Cookie(s)
Purpose
Essential Cookies - The site owner has indicated that these are essential to the running of the site.
CONCRETE5
This session id cookie remembers your recent page requests on our site and is required for the website to run. This cookie expires when you close your browser.
__sharethis_cookie_test__
Used to determine if cookies are supported
Non-Essential Cookies - The site owner has approved these cookies but you may turn them off.
Google Analytics
These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited.
Click here for an overview of privacy at Google(http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html)
Oracle Eloqua
(https://www.oracle.com/legal/privacy/index.html)
Evergage
(http://www.evergage.com/privacy-policy/)
ShareThis
(http://sharethis.com/privacy)
Uberflip
(https://www.uberflip.com/legal/privacy-policy/)
acuityplatform.com (auid)
https://acuityscheduling.com/privacy.php
adnxs.com (anj, sess, ssi, uuid2)
https://www.theguardian.com/info/privacy
ads.linkedin.com (BizoID, UserMatchHistory, lang)
Used for LinkedIn Ad analytics (Advertising)
https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy?src=direct%2Fnone&veh=direct%2Fnone%7Cdirect%2Fnone#
advertising.com (APID)
https://policies.oath.com/xw/en/oath/privacy/intl/index.html
bidswitch.net (c, tuuid_last_update, tuuid
http://www.bidswitch.com/privacy-policy/
Doubleclick.net (IDE)
https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en
exelator.com (EE, hsk_***, ud)
http://www.exelate.com/privacy/opt-in-opt-out/
facebook.com (fr)
https://www.facebook.com/policies/cookies/
go.flx1.com (check, id, r)
Advertising
infolinks.com (ANUSERCOOKIE, __cfduid)
Set to identify individual clients behind a shared IP address and to apply security settings on a per-client basis. For example, if the visitor is in a coffee shop where many machines are on the network, but the specific visitor's machine is trusted (e.g. because they've completed a challenge within your Challenge Passage period), the cookie allows us to identify that client and not challenge them again. It does not correspond to any user ID in your web application, and does not store any personally identifiable information.
https://www.infolinks.com/privacy-policy/
linkedin.com (bcookie, lidc)
https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy
mathtag.com (uuid, uuidc)
http://www.mediamath.com/privacy-policy/
mookie1.com (id, syncdata_DBC, mdata)
http://www.mookie1.com/en-us/privacy.html
Pardot
https://www.pardot.com/legal
rubiconproject.com (khaos, put_***, rpb, c, rpx)
Digital Identifiers created by Rubicon Project to aid in advertisements
https://rubiconproject.com/privacy/
scorecardresearch.com (UID, UIDR)
Set by scorecard research are related to market research, and may track your behaviour on our website.
http://www.scorecardresearch.com/privacy.aspx?newlanguage=1
sharethis.com (__stid)
Set as part of the ShareThis service and monitors "click-stream" activity, e.g. web pages viewed, navigation from page to page, time spent on each page etc. The ShareThis service only personally identifies you if you have separately signed up with ShareThis for a ShareThis account and given them your consent. You can read the ShareThis privacy policy here. This page also explains how you can opt out of the tracking aspects of the ShareThis Service if you wish to.
https://www.sharethis.com/privacy/
tribalfusion.com (ANON_ID)
http://exponential.com/privacy/
turn.com (uid)
https://www.amobee.com/trust/privacy-guidelines
v12group.com (mc)
http://www.v12data.com/v12-privacy-point-of-view/
veinteractive.com (__ssid, DFAB3643-4FF1-410F-925C-FF7CB7CEFA97)
Set to track abandoned transactions on our website
https://www.ve.com/privacy-policy .
videoamp.com (vampid)
https://secure.videoamp.com/privacy.html
volvelle.tech (ouuid, ouuid_last_update
http://www.optomaton.com/privacy.html
youtube.com (PREF, VISITOR_INFO1_LIVE, YSC)
Set by YouTube (Google) for storing user preferences and other unspecified purposes - https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en
Salesforce.com
Set to store information to track form submissionshttps://www.salesforce.com/company/privacy/
We are always available for a conversation.
We are always available for a conversation.
Submitting...
First Name
Last Name
Title
Company
Email Address
Country
Select Country
AfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBrazilBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaColombiaComorosCongoCosta RicaCroatia (Hrvatska)CubaCyprusCzech RepublicDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHondurasHungaryIcelandIndiaIsle of ManIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsraelItalyIvory CoastJerseyJamaicaJapanJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiNorth KoreaSouth KoreaKosovoKuwaitKyrgyzstanLaoLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyan Arab JamahiriyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMexicoMicronesia, Federated States ofMoldova, Republic ofMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestinePanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarReunionRomaniaRussian FederationRwandaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Vincent and the GrenadinesSamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSpainSri LankaSt. HelenaSt. Pierre and MiquelonSudanSurinameSvalbard and Jan Mayen IslandsSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandSyrian Arab RepublicTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited StatesUnited States minor outlying islandsUruguayUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuelaVietnamVirgin Islands (U.S.)Wallis and Futuna IslandsYemenZambiaZimbabwe
Comments
Communication Preference
Yes, I would like to receive marketing communications including industry insights and trends from Parexel International.
Communication Preference
I would like to receive marketing communications from Parexel and consent to the processing of the personal data that I provide in accordance with and as described in the Privacy Policy.
Accept
Decline
